<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
        <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        <description>HN posts' summary</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:36:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Feed for Node.js</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <image>
            <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
            <url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/b2/Y_Combinator_logo.svg/500px-Y_Combinator_logo.svg.png</url>
            <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        </image>
        <category>Frontpage</category>
        <atom:link href="https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Show HN: Conway's Game of Life in TypeScript's type system (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/RuyiLi/cursed-typescript/blob/master/random/game-of-life.ts</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/RuyiLi/cursed-typescript/blob/master/random/game-of-life.ts</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 19:11:47 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Code File for TypeScript Implementation of Game of Life]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a code file for a TypeScript implementation of the Game of Life. The code consists of 203 lines and is approximately 7.24 KB in size. It appears to be a random file within a larger project called 'cursed-typescript'.
            </p><p>
                66 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438028">11 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scammers Can Exploit Email Forwarding Flaws to Impersonate High-Profile Domains (today.ucsd.edu)]]></title>
            <link>https://today.ucsd.edu/story/forwarding_based_spoofing</link>
            <guid>https://today.ucsd.edu/story/forwarding_based_spoofing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 19:45:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Security Flaws in Email Forwarding Allow Scammers to Impersonate High-profile Domains]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researchers at the University of California San Diego have discovered security flaws in the email forwarding process that allow scammers to impersonate high-profile domains. This vulnerability affects tens of thousands of domains, including government organizations, financial service companies, and major news organizations. The researchers found that scammers can send spoofed emails that bypass the safeguards of email providers like Gmail and Outlook, increasing the likelihood of recipients opening malicious attachments or clicking on harmful links. The vulnerabilities arise from the delegation of email infrastructure to third-party providers and the assumption that each organization operates its own mailing infrastructure. While some providers have patched the issues, the researchers recommend disabling open forwarding and implementing stricter validation policies to address the root problem.
            </p><p>
                3 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438478">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aardvark'd: The Fog Creek documentary, 18 years later (mtlynch.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://mtlynch.io/aardvarkd/</link>
            <guid>https://mtlynch.io/aardvarkd/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:26:45 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Aardvark'd: The Fog Creek Documentary, 18 Years Later - A Look into the Early Days of Tech Startup Founders]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aardvark'd: The Fog Creek Documentary, 18 Years Later is a documentary film about Fog Creek's summer internship program in 2005. The film captures interviews with individuals who would go on to achieve fame and success in the tech industry. It explores the indie software scene of 2005, featuring Fog Creek Software, Y Combinator, and the launch of reddit. The documentary showcases the vulnerability and uncertainty experienced by tech startup founders during their early days. Despite its flaws, Aardvark'd provides a relatable and engaging look into the challenges of launching a software product. The film ends without a clear resolution, leaving viewers wondering about the outcome of the interns' project. The documentary includes insightful quotes from Paul Graham and Aaron Swartz. Surprisingly, Fog Creek did not finance the film, and the filmmaker recently uploaded it for free on YouTube.
            </p><p>
                282 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37433186">89 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Touch Pianist (touchpianist.com)]]></title>
            <link>http://touchpianist.com/</link>
            <guid>http://touchpianist.com/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:56:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Menu of Pieces on a Mobile App]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a brief summary of a menu or selection of pieces available on a mobile app. The menu offers the option to choose a different piece and provides information about the app and its creator. It mentions that the app is available for free on Android and iOS platforms. The content seems to be truncated, so it is difficult to provide a more detailed summary.
            </p><p>
                510 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37431644">166 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Just how constexpr is C++20’s std:string? (quuxplusone.github.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://quuxplusone.github.io/blog/2023/09/08/constexpr-string-firewall/</link>
            <guid>https://quuxplusone.github.io/blog/2023/09/08/constexpr-string-firewall/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:23:27 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the constexprness of C++20's std::string]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>C++20's std::string and std::vector can be marked as constexpr, allowing them to be used in compile-time programming. However, there are two constraints on constexprness: the value cannot depend on runtime input, and certain data cannot flow from compile-time into runtime. The article explains these constraints using examples of stack variables and memory addresses. It also discusses the limitations of constexpr string and vector, such as the inability to escape pointers to their data and the impact of small string optimization (SSO). The intended use of constexpr string and vector is as local variables or return types of constexpr or consteval functions, rather than as constexpr or constinit variables.
            </p><p>
                41 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37431425">24 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bun v1.0.0 (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/oven-sh/bun/releases/tag/bun-v1.0.0</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/oven-sh/bun/releases/tag/bun-v1.0.0</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 14:41:03 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bun v1.0 Release: Bug Fixes, Improvements, and New Features]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bun v1.0 is now available for installation and upgrade. The release notes highlight various bug fixes and improvements, including fixes for sourcemaps, hot reloading, module imports, debugger support, and more. The release also brings in uSockets and uWebSockets forks into Bun's repository. The changelog lists all the changes made from version 0.8.1 to 1.0.0. The release has seen contributions from new contributors as well. Overall, Bun v1.0 offers several enhancements and bug fixes for a better development experience.
            </p><p>
                586 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37434117">193 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maybe Rust isn’t a good tool for massively concurrent, userspace software (bitbashing.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://bitbashing.io/async-rust.html</link>
            <guid>https://bitbashing.io/async-rust.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 16:10:55 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Challenges and Limitations of Async Rust for Concurrency]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The article discusses the challenges and limitations of using async Rust for concurrency. It explains the difference between parallelism and concurrency and how breaking a problem into separate, independent parts can improve performance. The author explores the use of threads and mutex-based concurrency, highlighting the drawbacks and complexities involved. They then introduce the concept of channels as a synchronization mechanism and discuss how many modern languages, including Rust, provide channels in their standard libraries. The article also delves into the unique challenges of async Rust, such as the need to assure the compiler of data safety and the limitations of using Arc for dynamic lifetimes. Overall, the author suggests that while Rust may not be the best tool for massively concurrent, userspace software, it can still be valuable for other projects.
            </p><p>
                352 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37435515">299 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using LD_PRELOAD to cheat, inject features and investigate programs (rafalcieslak.wordpress.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://rafalcieslak.wordpress.com/2013/04/02/dynamic-linker-tricks-using-ld_preload-to-cheat-inject-features-and-investigate-programs/</link>
            <guid>https://rafalcieslak.wordpress.com/2013/04/02/dynamic-linker-tricks-using-ld_preload-to-cheat-inject-features-and-investigate-programs/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:41:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manipulating Application Behavior with LD_PRELOAD]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Using LD_PRELOAD to manipulate the behavior of applications
            </p><p>
                6 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37439125">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Learn Emacs (2012) (david.rothlis.net)]]></title>
            <link>https://david.rothlis.net/emacs/howtolearn.html</link>
            <guid>https://david.rothlis.net/emacs/howtolearn.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:16:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Mastering Emacs: A Guide for Programmers]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This guide to Emacs is aimed at computer programmers who want to master the text editor. It acknowledges that the learning curve for Emacs is steep but promises to help users reach the next level of programming in months rather than years. The guide emphasizes self-driven discovery using Emacs' built-in help, debugging facilities, and source code. The author asks for commitment and patience from readers, urging them to give up their favorite IDE's features for at least a month or two. The next section explores why Emacs is worth the effort.
            </p><p>
                7 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438842">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why we didn’t get a malaria vaccine sooner (worksinprogress.co)]]></title>
            <link>https://worksinprogress.co/issue/why-we-didnt-get-a-malaria-vaccine-sooner</link>
            <guid>https://worksinprogress.co/issue/why-we-didnt-get-a-malaria-vaccine-sooner</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 18:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Challenges and Delays in Developing a Malaria Vaccine]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The article discusses the challenges and delays in developing a malaria vaccine. It highlights the complexity of the malaria parasite and the lack of financial incentive and urgency as major obstacles. The discovery of the malaria parasite by Charles Laveran in 1880 is mentioned, along with the difficulties in finding a suitable animal model for vaccine development. The article also introduces the concept of Advance Market Commitments as a potential solution to encourage investment in vaccines for diseases affecting the global poor. Overall, the article emphasizes the need for innovative approaches to accelerate the development of vaccines for diseases like malaria.
            </p><p>
                51 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37437739">38 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zinc-air batteries as an alternative to lithium-ion: study (www.ecu.edu.au)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.ecu.edu.au/newsroom/articles/research/move-over-lithium-ion-zinc-air-batteries-a-cheaper-and-safer-alternative</link>
            <guid>https://www.ecu.edu.au/newsroom/articles/research/move-over-lithium-ion-zinc-air-batteries-a-cheaper-and-safer-alternative</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 15:49:56 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Zinc-air batteries identified as cheaper and safer alternative to lithium-ion batteries]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zinc-air batteries have been identified as a cheaper and safer alternative to lithium-ion batteries for powering electric vehicles, according to a study by Edith Cowan University. The research found that zinc-air batteries, which use a combination of sustainable and cost-effective materials, offer improved lifespan and performance compared to lithium-ion batteries. The breakthrough design of these batteries, using new materials such as carbon, iron, and cobalt, has overcome previous limitations related to power output and lifespan. The use of abundant zinc resources in countries like Australia, along with the ubiquity of air, makes zinc-air batteries a viable and reliable energy storage solution. This development contributes to building a sustainable society and reducing reliance on fossil fuels.
            </p><p>
                95 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37435215">71 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerabyte: ceramic storage poised to usher in 'yottabyte era' (www.tomshardware.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/cerabyte-ceramic-storage-poised-to-usher-in-yottabyte-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/cerabyte-ceramic-storage-poised-to-usher-in-yottabyte-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 16:49:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cerabyte's Ceramic Storage Technology Aims to Revolutionize the Market]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cerabyte, a German storage startup, claims that its ceramic nanolayer-based storage technology will disrupt the storage market by reducing data center storage TCO by 75%. The company plans to introduce CeraMemory cartridges (2025-30) with storage capacities between 10 PB and 100 PB, and CeraTape (2030-35) with up to 1 EB capacity per tape. Cerabyte's technology uses inorganic nanolayers to store information and can read and write data at GB/s class speeds. The company also highlights the durability and longevity of its ceramic storage, claiming that it can last over 5,000 years and withstand extreme temperatures and environments. Cerabyte's presentation at the 2023 Storage Developer Conference is highly anticipated.
            </p><p>
                28 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37436092">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards a New SymPy (oscarbenjamin.github.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://oscarbenjamin.github.io/blog/czi/post1.html</link>
            <guid>https://oscarbenjamin.github.io/blog/czi/post1.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:50:49 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Foundations of a Computer Algebra System: Towards a Faster SymPy]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Towards a Faster SymPy: Part 1 - Outlining the Foundations of a Computer Algebra System
            </p><p>
                62 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37430759">35 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FreeBSD pf bypass when using IPv6 (www.enricobassetti.it)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.enricobassetti.it/2023/09/cve-2023-4809-freebsd-pf-bypass-when-using-ipv6/</link>
            <guid>https://www.enricobassetti.it/2023/09/cve-2023-4809-freebsd-pf-bypass-when-using-ipv6/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 18:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[CVE-2023-4809: FreeBSD pf Bypass Vulnerability in IPv6 Firewalls]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CVE-2023-4809: FreeBSD pf bypass vulnerability allows attackers to bypass rules in pf-based IPv6 firewalls. The vulnerability occurs when a non-compliant IPv6 atomic fragment is sent, containing multiple IPv6 fragmentation headers. FreeBSD handles these fragments by rebuilding the original packet but fails to apply any rules that apply to layers four and higher. As a result, the fragment bypasses the firewall and establishes two-way communication between the attacker and the victim. The vulnerability affects all FreeBSD versions up to 13.2-STABLE and 12.4-STABLE. The solution is to update FreeBSD to the latest version.
            </p><p>
                47 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37437530">30 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artie (YC S23) is hiring a founding engineer (www.ycombinator.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/artie/jobs/PzBhYqV-founding-engineer</link>
            <guid>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/artie/jobs/PzBhYqV-founding-engineer</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 17:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Artie Seeks Founding Engineer for Real-Time Data Streaming Solution]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Artie is seeking a Founding Engineer to join their small team in San Francisco. The role involves working on distributed systems and data engineering, with responsibilities including setting up new data planes, optimizing their open-sourced service product, and adding functionality to the customer dashboard. The ideal candidate should have strong fundamentals in computer science, be pragmatic, and have experience with scaling asynchronous systems. Proficiency in Go is preferred. Artie is a real-time data streaming solution that focuses on databases and data warehouses, utilizing change data capture and stream processing for efficient data transfers with sub-minute latency.
            </p><p>
                1 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37436236">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Critical ignoring as a core competence for digital citizens (2022) (journals.sagepub.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/epub/10.1177/09637214221121570</link>
            <guid>https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/epub/10.1177/09637214221121570</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 03:36:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Website Security Check: journals.sagepub.com]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The website journals.sagepub.com is requesting to review the security of the user's connection before proceeding. This is likely due to concerns about potential security risks or vulnerabilities. The website is utilizing Cloudflare for performance and security purposes. The specific Ray ID provided is a unique identifier for the user's connection. It is important for users to ensure that their connection is secure before proceeding with any sensitive activities on the website.
            </p><p>
                119 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37428937">80 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The thinking path (www.robinsloan.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.robinsloan.com/newsletters/what-would-a-wizard-read/#walking</link>
            <guid>https://www.robinsloan.com/newsletters/what-would-a-wizard-read/#walking</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 21:52:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Robin Sloan's Excitement for His New Novel and Reflections on Creativity and Goodness]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robin Sloan announces the upcoming publication of his new novel in June 2024 and shares his excitement. He discusses the influence of fantasy sagas on his previous novels and explores the idea of going beyond homage to actively participate in the genre. Sloan plans to create a rich introduction and companion for his new novel, incorporating various influences and media. He also reviews a novel by Michiko Aoyama and reflects on the need for creative investigations of decency and goodness. Sloan asks for nominations of great author websites and discusses the problem-solving power of walking. He concludes by highlighting the quality of science journalism and sharing an interesting logo treatment for Mattel Electronics.
            </p><p>
                92 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37426107">20 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PgBouncer is useful, important, and fraught with peril (jpcamara.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://jpcamara.com/2023/04/12/pgbouncer-is-useful.html</link>
            <guid>https://jpcamara.com/2023/04/12/pgbouncer-is-useful.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:43:22 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Significance and Challenges of PgBouncer for Scaling PostgreSQL]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Understanding the importance and challenges of using PgBouncer for scaling PostgreSQL
            </p><p>
                162 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37431560">59 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GitHubGuessr (github-guessr.vercel.app)]]></title>
            <link>https://github-guessr.vercel.app/</link>
            <guid>https://github-guessr.vercel.app/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:09:44 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[N/A]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>N/A
            </p><p>
                32 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37432067">17 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digging through the New York Times morgue (buttondown.email)]]></title>
            <link>https://buttondown.email/linotypebook/archive/lbp-issue-no-5-digging-through-a-morgue/</link>
            <guid>https://buttondown.email/linotypebook/archive/lbp-issue-no-5-digging-through-a-morgue/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 21:53:14 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Uncovering Treasures: Exploring the Transition to Computer Phototypesetting at The New York Times]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researcher uncovers treasures from the transition to computer phototypesetting in the 1970s while digging through the New York Times morgue. The morgue contains millions of newspaper clippings, photographs, and other materials organized by subject matter. The researcher explores the transition from hot metal composition to computer phototypesetting at The Times in the 1970s, delving into the reasons behind the newspaper's delayed adoption of the technology. The visit to the morgue reveals internal publications documenting the transition and photos of the typesetting room. The researcher shares their process of organizing and analyzing the materials for their book on the topic.
            </p><p>
                25 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37426116">7 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emoji Generator with AI (emoji.fly.dev)]]></title>
            <link>https://emoji.fly.dev</link>
            <guid>https://emoji.fly.dev</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:54:13 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Collection of Diverse Emojis in Slackmoji AI Edition]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This collection of Slackmoji AI Edition features a wide range of emojis, including various characters, objects, and concepts. Some notable emojis include a bender, speedometer, flag of the most evil country, confused face, demon, Entei, Gopher, and a gray cat with a very long tongue. There are also emojis representing famous personalities like Donald Trump and Philip J. Fry. Additionally, there are emojis that depict controversial or inappropriate themes such as a gay Hitler and a Nazi. Overall, this collection offers a diverse range of emojis for users to express themselves in Slack conversations.
            </p><p>
                240 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37433523">115 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety inspector fired for finding 'too many defects' (jalopnik.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://jalopnik.com/safety-inspector-fired-for-finding-too-many-defects-cou-1850817520</link>
            <guid>https://jalopnik.com/safety-inspector-fired-for-finding-too-many-defects-cou-1850817520</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 18:51:07 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Safety Inspector Fired For Finding 'Too Many Defects' Exposes Culture of Ignoring Safety at Railroad Company]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Safety Inspector Fired For Finding 'Too Many Defects' Could Cost Railroad Millions. Former track inspector Don Sanders reveals a culture of ignoring safety in favor of profit at Burlington Northern Santa Fe (BNSF). Sanders had previously sued BNSF in 2017 for retaliation after reporting numerous defects. BNSF has a history of destroying evidence and retaliating against employees. Secretly recorded phone calls from the lawsuit expose BNSF's disregard for safety, with employees questioning why defects aren't fixed and supervisors discouraging calls to the Federal Railroad Administration. Other track inspectors confirm the pressure to overlook defects and the consequences of reporting them. Despite the evidence, Sanders' supervisor still has his job, received a raise, and a bonus.
            </p><p>
                133 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37437764">32 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[H2Fly – Breaking the Hydrogen Barrier (www.h2fly.de)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.h2fly.de/</link>
            <guid>https://www.h2fly.de/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:42:42 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Breaking the Hydrogen Barrier: Hydrogen's Potential to Decarbonize Aviation]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hydrogen is presented as the best solution for decarbonizing aviation due to its zero-emissions, safety, economic viability, low-noise profile, and ability to enable new regional air mobility connections. H2FLY, a German developer, has successfully completed the world's first piloted flight of an electric aircraft powered by liquid hydrogen. They have been researching and refining a hydrogen-electric powertrain system for over a decade, and their fuel cell system converts clean hydrogen into electricity to power their demonstrator aircraft HY4. This achievement proves that zero-emission aviation is within reach. H2FLY's vision is to unlock the era of sustainable air travel by developing qualified hydrogen-electric powertrains for aviation.
            </p><p>
                16 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37433380">12 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sieve: An Email Filtering Language (RFC5228) (www.rfc-editor.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.rfc-editor.org/info/rfc5228</link>
            <guid>https://www.rfc-editor.org/info/rfc5228</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 08:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sieve: An Email Filtering Language, a Proposed Standard]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sieve: An Email Filtering Language is a proposed standard that describes a language for filtering email messages at the time of final delivery. It can be implemented on both mail clients and servers, and is designed to be extensible, simple, and independent of access protocol, mail architecture, and operating system. The language is suitable for use on mail servers where users may not be allowed to execute arbitrary programs. It does not have variables, loops, or the ability to shell out to external programs. The document provides the definition of status and stream as per RFC standards.
            </p><p>
                3 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37416342">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FAA closes SpaceX Starship mishap investigation (apnews.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-starship-launch-accident-faa-a8d6cec63de579af4b6d5f040e51825d</link>
            <guid>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-starship-launch-accident-faa-a8d6cec63de579af4b6d5f040e51825d</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 16:19:12 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[FAA Requires SpaceX to Address Issues Before Launching Starship Mega Rocket Again]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SpaceX must address multiple issues and apply for a modified FAA license before launching its Starship mega rocket again, following its failed debut that ended in an explosion. The Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) has closed its investigation into the incident and has identified 63 corrective actions for SpaceX to take. The April launch explosion resulted in debris being scattered for thousands of feet and a plume of pulverized concrete spreading for miles. SpaceX founder Elon Musk has made improvements to the rocket and launch pad, and a new Starship is ready for liftoff. NASA plans to use Starship for moon landings, while Musk aims to build a fleet for Mars missions.
            </p><p>
                127 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37435656">115 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Show HN: Rivet – open-source AI Agent dev env with real-world applications (rivet.ironcladapp.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://rivet.ironcladapp.com/</link>
            <guid>https://rivet.ironcladapp.com/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:29:05 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Rivet: A Visual Programming Environment for Building AI Agents with LLMs]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rivet is a visual programming environment for building AI agents with LLMs. It allows teams to design, debug, and collaborate on complex LLM prompt graphs and deploy them in their own environment. The tool offers features like visualizing and building complex chains, remote debugging, and collaboration through versioning in a team's repository. Rivet has received positive feedback from users who appreciate its visual nature, debugging capabilities, and collaborative features. It has been used by Ironclad to develop their virtual contract assistant, Contract AI. Developers can easily get started with Rivet by following the provided guide and integrating it into their applications.
            </p><p>
                107 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37433218">26 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FTC judge decides Intuit’s ‘free’ TurboTax ads misled consumers (www.theverge.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/8/23864538/turbotax-intuit-ftc-deceptive-practices-free-tax-filing</link>
            <guid>https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/8/23864538/turbotax-intuit-ftc-deceptive-practices-free-tax-filing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 18:19:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[FTC Judge Finds Intuit's 'Free' TurboTax Ads Misled Consumers]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTC judge rules that Intuit's 'free' TurboTax ads were misleading, finding that the company deceived consumers by advertising its tax filing service as free when users had to pay to use it. The ruling includes evidence of commercials and online ads promoting the 'Free Edition' software. Intuit was also criticized for making its actually free Free File version difficult to find. The judge issued a cease-and-desist order, prohibiting Intuit from engaging in deceptive practices and requiring clear disclosure of any terms that would limit offers. Intuit responded by calling the investigation process flawed and questionable, stating that it already adheres to most advertising practices in the FTC's decision. The IRS is working on a government-backed free filing service for the 2024 tax season.
            </p><p>
                208 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37437311">59 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASMesh: Anonymous, Secure Messaging in Mesh Networks (eprint.iacr.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2023/1053</link>
            <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2023/1053</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:24:25 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ASMesh: Anonymous and Secure Messaging in Mesh Networks Using Stronger, Anonymous Double Ratchet]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ASMesh is a new protocol that provides anonymous and secure messaging in mesh networks. It addresses the limitations of centralized service providers in scenarios like mass protests in censored networks. The protocol is designed to achieve forward and post-compromise security, as well as forward and post-compromise anonymity. It builds on Signal's Double Ratchet protocol and introduces enhancements to ensure strong confidentiality and anonymity under user corruptions. The protocol's security is proven and its performance is evaluated in simulated mesh networks. The paper also includes a proof of concept implementation.
            </p><p>
                5 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37431433">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bees struggle to find flowers because of air pollution (www.birmingham.ac.uk)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.birmingham.ac.uk/news/2023/bees-struggle-to-find-flowers-because-of-air-pollution</link>
            <guid>https://www.birmingham.ac.uk/news/2023/bees-struggle-to-find-flowers-because-of-air-pollution</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 14:59:13 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Air pollution degrades floral scent, making it difficult for bees to find flowers]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Air pollution degrades the scent of flowers, making it difficult for bees to find them, according to a study by the UK Centre for Ecology & Hydrology and several universities. The research found that ground-level ozone, formed when nitrogen oxide emissions react with volatile organic compounds, changes the size and scent of floral odour plumes. This reduced honeybees' ability to recognise odours by up to 90% from just a few metres away. The study suggests that ozone could have a negative impact on wildflower abundance and crop yields, with implications for food security. The research highlights the need to take action on air pollution to protect pollinators and preserve biodiversity.
            </p><p>
                121 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37434381">24 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consumers defrauded on Zelle are left high and dry by the banks that created it [pdf] (news.ycombinator.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438934</link>
            <guid>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438934</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:23:45 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No summary available
            </p><p>
                20 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438934">3 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>