<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
        <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        <description>HN posts' summary</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 20:37:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Feed for Node.js</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <image>
            <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
            <url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/b2/Y_Combinator_logo.svg/500px-Y_Combinator_logo.svg.png</url>
            <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        </image>
        <category>Frontpage</category>
        <atom:link href="https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asking 60 LLMs a set of 20 questions (benchmarks.llmonitor.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://benchmarks.llmonitor.com</link>
            <guid>https://benchmarks.llmonitor.com</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Script Tests Reasoning and Creativity of 60+ Models Using Prompts']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A script was created to ask prompts testing reasoning, instruction following, and creativity to around 60 models. The answers were stored in a SQLite database. The prompts covered various topics such as arguing for and against the use of Kubernetes, explaining quantum field theory to a high-school student, and finding the next 20 leap years. The script used a mix of APIs from different platforms. The creator plans to improve the script by using better stop sequences and prompt formatting tailored to each model.
            </p><p>
                359 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445401">219 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I used a Game Boy camera for Facetime video calls in iPadOS 17 (www.macstories.net)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.macstories.net/stories/i-used-a-game-boy-camera-for-facetime-video-calls-in-ipados-17-and-it-was-glorious/</link>
            <guid>https://www.macstories.net/stories/i-used-a-game-boy-camera-for-facetime-video-calls-in-ipados-17-and-it-was-glorious/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 02:26:44 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['I Used a Game Boy Camera for FaceTime Video Calls in iPadOS 17 and It Was Glorious']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>iPadOS 17 now supports UVC (USB Video Class) devices, allowing iPads to recognize external webcams, cameras, and other devices connected over USB-C. Federico Viticci tested this feature and found that he could use a Game Boy Camera as his iPad Pro's webcam during FaceTime calls. He also experimented with using a game capture card to play Nintendo Switch and Steam Deck games on his iPad's display. This unexpected functionality showcases the versatility of iPadOS 17 and its potential for creative and gaming applications.
            </p><p>
                17 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37428491">4 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Show HN: I built a Python web framework from scratch (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/ZeroIntensity/view.py</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/ZeroIntensity/view.py</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 18:47:54 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['view.py: A Lightning-Fast and Modern Web Framework in Alpha Stage']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>view.py is a lightning-fast, modern web framework that is currently in a high alpha stage of development. It requires CPython 3.8+ for installation. The framework offers a simple and efficient way to build web applications. It is actively seeking new contributors and provides installation instructions for Linux/macOS and Windows. view.py aims to provide a fast and modern solution for web development.
            </p><p>
                22 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37448914">4 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Every type of plastic used by LEGO (2022) (bricknerd.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://bricknerd.com/home/every-type-of-plastic-used-by-lego-5-20-22</link>
            <guid>https://bricknerd.com/home/every-type-of-plastic-used-by-lego-5-20-22</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 11:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Many Types of Plastic Used By LEGO]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LEGO uses a variety of plastics for their bricks, including CA, HIPS, Bakelite, ABS, SAN, PP, PC, MABS, PA, POM, TP, PE, MTPO, TPU, SEBS, and PET. Each plastic has its own properties and uses, with ABS being the most commonly used since 1963. LEGO is also investing in developing sustainable materials and has already started using plant-sourced polyethylene and phasing out plastic shopping bags.
            </p><p>
                249 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444268">76 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAROL6 Desktop Robot Arm (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/PCrnjak/PAROL6-Desktop-robot-arm</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/PCrnjak/PAROL6-Desktop-robot-arm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 14:37:45 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['PAROL6: A High-Performance 3D-Printed Desktop Robotic Arm with Open-Source Design']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PAROL6 is a high-performance 3D-printed desktop robotic arm that aims to mimic industrial robots in terms of design and usability. The control software, GUI, and STL files are open-source, allowing users to build their own PAROL6 robot by following the provided instructions. The project welcomes donations, advice, and contributions to support its open-source nature. The code and STL files are under the GPLv3 License.
            </p><p>
                49 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445951">12 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dennis Austin, developer of PowerPoint, has died (www.washingtonpost.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/obituaries/2023/09/08/dennis-austin-software-developer-powerpoint-dies/</link>
            <guid>https://www.washingtonpost.com/obituaries/2023/09/08/dennis-austin-software-developer-powerpoint-dies/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Dennis Austin, Principal Software Developer of PowerPoint, Dies at 76']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dennis Austin, the principal software developer of PowerPoint, has passed away at the age of 76. Austin played a significant role in shaping how information is communicated in modern society through the development of PowerPoint. The software, which was released in 1987, revolutionized the creation of slides and became a ubiquitous tool in offices, classrooms, and government agencies. Despite its widespread use, PowerPoint has also faced criticism for its potential to create mind-numbing presentations filled with bullet points. Austin's contributions to the software were instrumental in its success.
            </p><p>
                25 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37440696">94 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Show HN: WhatsApp-Llama: A clone of yourself from your WhatsApp conversations (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/Ads-cmu/WhatsApp-Llama</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/Ads-cmu/WhatsApp-Llama</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Fine-tune Llama 7b to Mimic Your WhatsApp Style]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This repository is a fork of the facebookresearch/llama-recipes, adapted to fine-tune a Llama 7b chat model to replicate your personal WhatsApp texting style. The fine-tuned Llama model picked up on the user's texting nuances rapidly and accurately replicated common phrases and emoji usage. In a Turing Test with friends, the model fooled 10% of them, with some responses being eerily similar to the user's own. The adaptation of the Llama model offers a fun way to see how well a LLM can mimic your personal texting style.
            </p><p>
                16 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37448005">2 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The era-defining aesthetic of “In the Mood for Love” (www.newyorker.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/touchstones/wong-kar-wais-in-the-mood-for-love</link>
            <guid>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/touchstones/wong-kar-wais-in-the-mood-for-love</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 23:55:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['In the Mood for Love': Wong Kar Wai's Influential Masterpiece]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wong Kar Wai's 2000 film 'In the Mood for Love' has had a significant influence on popular culture, with its unique aesthetic and storytelling. The film, set in 1960s Hong Kong, follows two individuals who discover that their spouses are having an affair and become entangled themselves. Wong's personal history and diverse influences shaped the film's style, which combines elements of French New Wave filmmaking, American mystery, and Chinese literature. 'In the Mood for Love' is a visually stunning and emotionally resonant work that continues to captivate audiences.
            </p><p>
                9 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37413027">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Birth of the Gentoo Linux Distribution (www.funtoo.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.funtoo.org/Making_the_Distribution,_Part_1</link>
            <guid>https://www.funtoo.org/Making_the_Distribution,_Part_1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 15:29:14 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['The Potential of Linux and Dealing with Difficult Developers: Daniel Robbins' Linux Journey']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Robbins shares his Linux journey, from becoming a Stampede Linux developer to starting his own distribution called Enoch. He emphasizes the potential of Linux to change, improve, and break things, as well as the importance of the Linux community. Robbins also discusses his experience dealing with difficult developers and offers advice on managing them.
            </p><p>
                19 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37446509">1 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A small-town police officer took down a large match-fixing ring in tennis (news.ycombinator.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37432336</link>
            <guid>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37432336</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:49:55 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No summary available
            </p><p>
                38 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37432336">32 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DJI Virtual Flight (iOS) has been broken for five months (forum.dji.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://forum.dji.com/thread-293546-1-1.html</link>
            <guid>https://forum.dji.com/thread-293546-1-1.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 14:38:53 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Collection of Tutorials, Tips, and Information on Drones and DJI Products]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a collection of various tutorials, tips, and information related to drones, handheld devices, post-production, and other topics. It also includes a list of DJI products, such as the Mavic Series, FPV Series, and Osmo, as well as different works and events. The article also includes some JavaScript code related to search functionality and user interaction.
            </p><p>
                105 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445963">71 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Order of the Occult Hand (en.wikipedia.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Order_of_the_Occult_Hand</link>
            <guid>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Order_of_the_Occult_Hand</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 19:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Order of the Occult Hand: A Secret Society of Journalists]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Order of the Occult Hand is a secret society of American journalists who insert the phrase 'It was as if an occult hand had...' into their articles as an inside joke. The phrase was introduced by Joseph Flanders in 1965, and his colleagues formed the Order to commemorate it. The tradition spread to other media outlets and even internationally. The Order's secrecy was exposed in 2004, but it continues to operate and has chosen a new secret phrase in 2006. In 2020, a journalism challenge was announced to encourage the use of a meaningless telltale phrase in news articles.
            </p><p>
                12 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37449620">2 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[English cottage where John le Carré wrote Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy is for sale (lithub.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://lithub.com/look-inside-the-gorgeous-english-cottage-where-john-le-carre-wrote-tinker-tailor-soldier-spy/</link>
            <guid>https://lithub.com/look-inside-the-gorgeous-english-cottage-where-john-le-carre-wrote-tinker-tailor-soldier-spy/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 19:34:44 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['John Le Carré's Cornwall Home, Tregiffian Cottage, Hits the Market for $3.7 Million']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Le Carré's Cornwall home, Tregiffian Cottage, is up for sale for $3.7 million. The 5,000-square-foot house, where Le Carré wrote many of his novels, features a detached writing studio, a library with bespoke joinery, and a safe room. The property offers stunning views and a picturesque setting. Le Carré's son, Nick Cornwell, described the cottage as a place filled with wildlife and natural beauty, making it an ideal space for rest, work, or self-reflection.
            </p><p>
                3 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37449439">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intel announces Arm investment, talks up RISC-V (www.tomshardware.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/intel-confirms-arm-investment-arm-and-risc-v-is-where-the-volumes-are</link>
            <guid>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/intel-confirms-arm-investment-arm-and-risc-v-is-where-the-volumes-are</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:32:48 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intel Invests in Arm Holdings, Recognizing the Importance of Arm's Technology]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Intel has announced that it has made an investment in Arm Holdings, joining the list of Arm's anchor investors. The head of Intel's foundry business unit confirmed that the investment was made because Arm's technology is strategically important for both Intel Foundry Services and Altera FPGA unit. Intel recognizes the importance of Arm's instruction set architecture (ISA) in a wide range of applications and aims to collaborate further with Arm in the future.
            </p><p>
                90 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37415804">38 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Existing in an Un-Simulated Reality (iahwrites.substack.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://iahwrites.substack.com/p/existing-in-an-un-simulated-reality</link>
            <guid>https://iahwrites.substack.com/p/existing-in-an-un-simulated-reality</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:27:52 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Existence in an Un-Simulated Reality: A Theory on the Feeling of Consciousness']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author proposes a theory that even if a simulation of reality is never run, it would still feel real to the actors inside it. This theory is based on the idea that all possible states of a complex system already exist, and calculating them is not necessary for them to feel conscious. The author acknowledges that this theory does not negate the existence of choice and plans to explore community in NYC in future posts.
            </p><p>
                17 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37447810">16 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Development of the C Language (2003) (cm.bell-labs.co)]]></title>
            <link>http://cm.bell-labs.co/who/dmr/chist.html</link>
            <guid>http://cm.bell-labs.co/who/dmr/chist.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 06:33:32 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['The Development and Evolution of the C Programming Language']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This paper discusses the development of the C programming language, its influences, and the conditions under which it was created. It highlights the evolution of C from its parent language BCPL and its grandparent language BCPL. The paper also mentions the significant periods of changes in the language and its association with the Unix operating system. It concludes by noting that C has become one of the dominant languages in the computer industry today.
            </p><p>
                142 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37442810">20 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why you might want async in your project (notgull.net)]]></title>
            <link>https://notgull.net/why-you-want-async/</link>
            <guid>https://notgull.net/why-you-want-async/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 18:17:56 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Why you might actually want async in your project']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author argues that the sentiment in the Rust community that async/await is only useful for a small number of programs is misguided. They believe that actively shying away from async is the wrong approach and that many Rust projects are already using async/await without realizing it. The author also addresses the reasons why some people may not like async, such as poor advertising and standard library support. They conclude by encouraging Rustaceans to embrace async/await and explore its benefits.
            </p><p>
                69 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37448460">51 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public restrooms are hard to find in America (www.washingtonpost.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/09/08/public-restrooms-hard-find-comic/</link>
            <guid>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/09/08/public-restrooms-hard-find-comic/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 14:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['The Problem of Inaccessible Public Restrooms in America']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Public restrooms are hard to find in America, with only eight public toilets for every 100,000 people. This poses a problem for millions of Americans suffering from medical conditions, as well as unhoused individuals, older adults, and pregnant individuals. The lack of accessible public restrooms can lead to anxiety and avoidance of going out. This article highlights the importance of addressing this issue for the well-being of various populations.
            </p><p>
                111 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37446083">255 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The U.S. housing market vs. the Canadian housing market (awealthofcommonsense.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/09/the-u-s-housing-market-vs-the-canadian-housing-market/</link>
            <guid>https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/09/the-u-s-housing-market-vs-the-canadian-housing-market/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 15:54:15 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Canadian Housing Prices Continue to Soar, Outpacing U.S. Market]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Canadian housing prices have continued to rise at an alarming rate, with a 142% increase since 2005 on a real basis. This is in stark contrast to the U.S. housing market, which has seen a more modest 26% increase over the same period. The differences between the two markets become even more pronounced when comparing housing price gains to disposable income gains. While U.S. incomes have kept pace with housing prices, Canadian incomes have not, leading to a significant affordability issue in Canada.
            </p><p>
                140 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37446790">328 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Berkeley Hotel Hostage of Douglas Adams (www.thebookseller.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thebookseller.com/features/berkeley-hotel-hostage</link>
            <guid>https://www.thebookseller.com/features/berkeley-hotel-hostage</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 11:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[N/A]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>N/A
            </p><p>
                57 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444066">15 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FFmpeg Patches for a 20% speedup of Apple ProRes decoding (ffmpeg.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://ffmpeg.org/pipermail/ffmpeg-devel/2023-September/314167.html</link>
            <guid>https://ffmpeg.org/pipermail/ffmpeg-devel/2023-September/314167.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 15:23:10 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['FFmpeg' Patch Improves Proresdec2 Performance with Cached Reader]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This patch for FFmpeg's proresdec2 fixes and ports the cached reader. The changes include moving back to the regular get_bits API, reducing the lookup to switch the coding method, and using shorter reads for the end of the bitstream. The patch also provides speedup results for Win64 and Win32 platforms. The cached reader version shows a 20% speedup on Win64 and a 14% speedup on Win32.
            </p><p>
                17 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37446430">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skio (YC S20) Is Hiring – Subscriptions for Shopify, ReCharge migrations (skio.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://skio.com/careers/</link>
            <guid>https://skio.com/careers/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Skio: A Startup Helping Brands Sell Subscriptions on Shopify with a Unique Business Model']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Skio is a startup that helps brands on Shopify sell subscriptions and stands out with its transaction fee business model. The company has a flat organizational structure, minimal meeting culture, and a big long-term vision for building network effects. The founder, Kennan, has a track record of success and an EV-based decision-making approach. Skio is currently hiring for various positions in engineering, product, sales, customer experience, growth, and more.
            </p><p>
                1 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444354">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bare-Metal Kubernetes, Part I: Talos on Hetzner (datavirke.dk)]]></title>
            <link>https://datavirke.dk/posts/bare-metal-kubernetes-part-1-talos-on-hetzner/</link>
            <guid>https://datavirke.dk/posts/bare-metal-kubernetes-part-1-talos-on-hetzner/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 08:44:52 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building a Kubernetes Cluster with Talos on Hetzner: Part I]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author shares their experience of running a Kubernetes cluster on a mix of virtual and bare metal machines with Hetzner. They decide to rebuild the cluster from scratch and document the process in a series of blog posts. The first part covers provisioning the first server, installing Talos Linux, and configuration and bootstrapping.
            </p><p>
                163 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37443404">57 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eio 1.0 – Effects-based IO for OCaml 5 (icfp23.sigplan.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://icfp23.sigplan.org/details/ocaml-2023-papers/5/Eio-1-0-Effects-based-IO-for-OCaml-5</link>
            <guid>https://icfp23.sigplan.org/details/ocaml-2023-papers/5/Eio-1-0-Effects-based-IO-for-OCaml-5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 08:44:07 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Eio 1.0 - Effects-based IO for OCaml 5' to be Presented at ICFP 2023]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This session at ICFP 2023 will discuss Eio 1.0, an effects-based IO stack for OCaml 5. The talk will cover its main features, including multi-core support, lock-free data structures, modular programming, interoperability with other concurrency libraries, and interactive monitoring support. The speakers will also share their experiences in porting existing applications to Eio.
            </p><p>
                7 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37443395">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Half of Glaciers Vanish with 1.5 Degrees of Warming (www.nasa.gov)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.nasa.gov/feature/esnt/2023/nasa-funded-study-half-of-glaciers-vanish-with-1-point-5-degrees-of-warming/</link>
            <guid>https://www.nasa.gov/feature/esnt/2023/nasa-funded-study-half-of-glaciers-vanish-with-1-point-5-degrees-of-warming/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['NASA Study: Glaciers Could Lose 40% of Mass by 2100 Due to Global Warming']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A study funded by NASA predicts that glaciers around the world could lose up to 40% of their mass by 2100 due to global warming. With a temperature increase of 1.5 degrees Celsius, 50% of the world's glaciers would disappear and contribute to a 9 centimeter rise in sea levels by 2100. If warming reaches 4 degrees Celsius, 80% of the world's glaciers will disappear and contribute to a 15 centimeter rise in sea levels. The study emphasizes the importance of taking action to mitigate climate change.
            </p><p>
                46 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37449413">13 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRISPR used to 'reprogram' cancer cells into healthy muscle in the lab (news.ycombinator.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444477</link>
            <guid>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444477</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:20:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No summary available
            </p><p>
                151 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444477">24 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google's Statement on the UK Online Safety Bill (bills.parliament.uk)]]></title>
            <link>https://bills.parliament.uk/publications/46675/documents/1885</link>
            <guid>https://bills.parliament.uk/publications/46675/documents/1885</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:36:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Security Check on bills.parliament.uk]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The website bills.parliament.uk is checking the security of the user's connection before proceeding. It is using Cloudflare for performance and security. The Ray ID provided is 803f9d175da16464.
            </p><p>
                48 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37443634">27 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What happens when you shift a register by more than the register size? (devblogs.microsoft.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230904-00/?p=108704</link>
            <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230904-00/?p=108704</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 22:39:13 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Different Processor Architectures Behave Differently When Shifting Registers]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When shifting a register by more than its size, different processor architectures exhibit different behaviors. The table provided in the article shows the behavior of various processors, including the 8086, Alpha AXP, x86-64, MIPS, PowerPC, and more. The article also mentions that the C and C++ languages leave the behavior undefined when shifting by more than the bit width of the shifted type.
            </p><p>
                78 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37426598">52 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Telescript (programming language) (en.wikipedia.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Telescript_(programming_language)</link>
            <guid>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Telescript_(programming_language)</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 04:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Telescript: An Agent-Oriented Programming Language for Uploading Programs to Servers']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Telescript is an agent-oriented programming language developed by General Magic as part of the Magic Cap system. It allowed end-user devices to upload programs to servers and take advantage of their capabilities. However, General Magic failed to find a niche in the market and Telescript services were eventually deprecated. The language was object-oriented and used a modified C-like syntax. It introduced the concepts of agents and places, which interacted with each other to perform tasks.
            </p><p>
                32 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37429362">17 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The end of the subscription era is coming (nickfthilton.medium.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://nickfthilton.medium.com/the-end-of-the-subscription-era-is-coming-ed197f252c6a</link>
            <guid>https://nickfthilton.medium.com/the-end-of-the-subscription-era-is-coming-ed197f252c6a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:36:41 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Impact of Subscription Models on Media and Creators]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rise of subscription models in various industries, including media, has had a significant impact on the way businesses operate and how creators earn income. While platforms like Substack and OnlyFans offer potential for lucrative earnings, the average writer or creator may earn very little. Additionally, the increasing reliance on subscriptions for various products and services raises questions about the sustainability and affordability of this model for consumers. The cost of living crisis and the need for supplemental income in a challenging job market contribute to the appeal of these platforms for creators.
            </p><p>
                93 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37447915">86 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>