<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
        <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        <description>HN posts' summary</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 18:37:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Feed for Node.js</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <image>
            <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
            <url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/b2/Y_Combinator_logo.svg/500px-Y_Combinator_logo.svg.png</url>
            <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        </image>
        <category>Frontpage</category>
        <atom:link href="https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asking 60 LLMs a set of 20 questions (benchmarks.llmonitor.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://benchmarks.llmonitor.com</link>
            <guid>https://benchmarks.llmonitor.com</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Script Tests Reasoning and Creativity of 60+ Models Using Prompts']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A script was created to ask prompts testing reasoning, instruction following, and creativity to around 60 models. The answers were stored in a SQLite database. The prompts covered various topics such as arguing for and against the use of Kubernetes, explaining quantum field theory to a high-school student, and finding the next 20 leap years. The script used a mix of APIs from different platforms. The creator plans to improve the script by using better stop sequences and prompt formatting tailored to each model.
            </p><p>
                229 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445401">135 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Every type of plastic used by Lego (2022) (bricknerd.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://bricknerd.com/home/every-type-of-plastic-used-by-lego-5-20-22</link>
            <guid>https://bricknerd.com/home/every-type-of-plastic-used-by-lego-5-20-22</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 11:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Many Types of Plastic Used By LEGO]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LEGO uses a variety of plastics for their bricks, including CA, HIPS, Bakelite, ABS, SAN, PP, PC, MABS, PA, POM, TP, PE, MTPO, TPU, SEBS, and PET. Each plastic has its own properties and uses, with ABS being the most commonly used since 1963. LEGO is also investing in developing sustainable materials and has already started using plant-sourced polyethylene and phasing out plastic shopping bags.
            </p><p>
                197 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444268">55 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intel Announces Arm Investment, Talks Up RISC-V (www.tomshardware.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/intel-confirms-arm-investment-arm-and-risc-v-is-where-the-volumes-are</link>
            <guid>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/intel-confirms-arm-investment-arm-and-risc-v-is-where-the-volumes-are</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:32:48 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intel Invests in Arm Holdings, Recognizing the Importance of Arm's Technology]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Intel has announced that it has made an investment in Arm Holdings, joining the list of Arm's anchor investors. The head of Intel's foundry business unit confirmed that the investment was made because Arm's technology is strategically important for both Intel Foundry Services and Altera FPGA unit. Intel recognizes the importance of Arm's instruction set architecture (ISA) in a wide range of applications and aims to collaborate further with Arm in the future.
            </p><p>
                33 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37415804">4 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DJI Virtual Flight (iOS) has been broken for five months (forum.dji.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://forum.dji.com/thread-293546-1-1.html</link>
            <guid>https://forum.dji.com/thread-293546-1-1.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 14:38:53 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Collection of Tutorials, Tips, and Information on Drones and DJI Products]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a collection of various tutorials, tips, and information related to drones, handheld devices, post-production, and other topics. It also includes a list of DJI products, such as the Mavic Series, FPV Series, and Osmo, as well as different works and events. The article also includes some JavaScript code related to search functionality and user interaction.
            </p><p>
                75 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445963">41 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAROL6 Desktop Robot Arm (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/PCrnjak/PAROL6-Desktop-robot-arm</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/PCrnjak/PAROL6-Desktop-robot-arm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 14:37:45 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['PAROL6: A High-Performance 3D-Printed Desktop Robotic Arm with Open-Source Design']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PAROL6 is a high-performance 3D-printed desktop robotic arm that aims to mimic industrial robots in terms of design and usability. The control software, GUI, and STL files are open-source, allowing users to build their own PAROL6 robot by following the provided instructions. The project welcomes donations, advice, and contributions to support its open-source nature. The code and STL files are under the GPLv3 License.
            </p><p>
                49 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445951">12 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Development of the M1 Garand and Its Implications (acoup.blog)]]></title>
            <link>https://acoup.blog/2023/09/08/michael-taylor-on-the-development-of-the-m1-garand-and-its-implications/</link>
            <guid>https://acoup.blog/2023/09/08/michael-taylor-on-the-development-of-the-m1-garand-and-its-implications/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 08:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['The M1 Garand: A Missed Opportunity for US Rifle Development']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The M1 Garand, considered the best battle rifle of World War II, had a significant impact on subsequent US rifle development. While it provided advantages such as increased rate of fire and improved accuracy, it missed the opportunity to become a modern assault rifle. The US did not field its first true assault rifle until two decades after the concept was invented by the Germans. The article explores the development of the M1 Garand and the factors that influenced its design.
            </p><p>
                58 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37430842">33 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The End of the Subscription Era Is Coming (nickfthilton.medium.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://nickfthilton.medium.com/the-end-of-the-subscription-era-is-coming-ed197f252c6a</link>
            <guid>https://nickfthilton.medium.com/the-end-of-the-subscription-era-is-coming-ed197f252c6a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:36:41 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Impact of Subscription Models on Media and Creators]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rise of subscription models in various industries, including media, has had a significant impact on the way businesses operate and how creators earn income. While platforms like Substack and OnlyFans offer potential for lucrative earnings, the average writer or creator may earn very little. Additionally, the increasing reliance on subscriptions for various products and services raises questions about the sustainability and affordability of this model for consumers. The cost of living crisis and the need for supplemental income in a challenging job market contribute to the appeal of these platforms for creators.
            </p><p>
                7 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37447915">1 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A History of Carrying Capacity (www.wsj.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.wsj.com/arts-culture/books/pockets-review-carrying-capacity-2245357a</link>
            <guid>https://www.wsj.com/arts-culture/books/pockets-review-carrying-capacity-2245357a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 16:43:12 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Equality in Pockets': The Fight for Gender Equality in Clothing]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the late 19th century, women demanded 'equality in pockets' as they noticed a divergence in the development and availability of pockets in men's and women's clothing. This article highlights the historical context of pockets and how they became a symbol of gender inequality. The demand for equal pockets was seen as a part of the broader fight for women's rights, including the right to vote.
            </p><p>
                6 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37447315">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The U.S. housing market vs. the Canadian housing market (awealthofcommonsense.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/09/the-u-s-housing-market-vs-the-canadian-housing-market/</link>
            <guid>https://awealthofcommonsense.com/2023/09/the-u-s-housing-market-vs-the-canadian-housing-market/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 15:54:15 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Canadian Housing Prices Continue to Soar, Outpacing U.S. Market]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Canadian housing prices have continued to rise at an alarming rate, with a 142% increase since 2005 on a real basis. This is in stark contrast to the U.S. housing market, which has seen a more modest 26% increase over the same period. The differences between the two markets become even more pronounced when comparing housing price gains to disposable income gains. While U.S. incomes have kept pace with housing prices, Canadian incomes have not, leading to a significant affordability issue in Canada.
            </p><p>
                74 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37446790">145 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heat pumps show how hard decarbonisation will be (www.economist.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/09/06/heat-pumps-show-how-hard-decarbonisation-will-be</link>
            <guid>https://www.economist.com/leaders/2023/09/06/heat-pumps-show-how-hard-decarbonisation-will-be</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:21:14 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Resistance to Heat Pumps Highlights Challenges of Decarbonization']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The adoption of heat pumps as an alternative to gas and oil boilers is crucial for decarbonization efforts in Europe. However, the push for green policies that require citizens to make disruptive changes to their lives is facing resistance. Heat pumps have become a symbol of the challenges and backlashes that come with decarbonization. This highlights the difficulty of achieving decarbonization goals and the need for effective communication and support for individuals during the transition.
            </p><p>
                4 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37447740">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A small-town police officer took down the largest matchfixing ring in tennis (www.msn.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/tennis/the-unraveling-how-a-small-town-police-officer-took-down-the-largest-match-fixing-ring-in-tennis/ar-AA1gmhhx</link>
            <guid>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/tennis/the-unraveling-how-a-small-town-police-officer-took-down-the-largest-match-fixing-ring-in-tennis/ar-AA1gmhhx</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 16:21:10 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[N/A]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>N/A
            </p><p>
                23 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37447080">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Development of the C Language (2003) (cm.bell-labs.co)]]></title>
            <link>http://cm.bell-labs.co/who/dmr/chist.html</link>
            <guid>http://cm.bell-labs.co/who/dmr/chist.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 06:33:32 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['The Development and Evolution of the C Programming Language']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This paper discusses the development of the C programming language, its influences, and the conditions under which it was created. It highlights the evolution of C from its parent language BCPL and its grandparent language BCPL. The paper also mentions the significant periods of changes in the language and its association with the Unix operating system. It concludes by noting that C has become one of the dominant languages in the computer industry today.
            </p><p>
                142 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37442810">20 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bare-Metal Kubernetes, Part I: Talos on Hetzner (datavirke.dk)]]></title>
            <link>https://datavirke.dk/posts/bare-metal-kubernetes-part-1-talos-on-hetzner/</link>
            <guid>https://datavirke.dk/posts/bare-metal-kubernetes-part-1-talos-on-hetzner/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 08:44:52 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building a Kubernetes Cluster with Talos on Hetzner: Part I]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author shares their experience of running a Kubernetes cluster on a mix of virtual and bare metal machines with Hetzner. They decide to rebuild the cluster from scratch and document the process in a series of blog posts. The first part covers provisioning the first server, installing Talos Linux, and configuration and bootstrapping.
            </p><p>
                101 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37443404">32 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Berkeley Hotel Hostage of Douglas Adams (www.thebookseller.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.thebookseller.com/features/berkeley-hotel-hostage</link>
            <guid>https://www.thebookseller.com/features/berkeley-hotel-hostage</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 11:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[N/A]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>N/A
            </p><p>
                8 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444066">1 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRISPR used to 'reprogram' cancer cells into healthy muscle in the lab (news.ycombinator.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444477</link>
            <guid>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444477</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:20:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No summary available
            </p><p>
                115 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444477">17 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skio (YC S20) – Subscriptions for Shopify, ReCharge Migrations Is Hiring (skio.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://skio.com/careers/</link>
            <guid>https://skio.com/careers/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Skio: A Startup Helping Brands Sell Subscriptions on Shopify with a Unique Business Model']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Skio is a startup that helps brands on Shopify sell subscriptions and stands out with its transaction fee business model. The company has a flat organizational structure, minimal meeting culture, and a big long-term vision for building network effects. The founder, Kennan, has a track record of success and an EV-based decision-making approach. Skio is currently hiring for various positions in engineering, product, sales, customer experience, growth, and more.
            </p><p>
                1 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444354">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dennis Austin, developer of PowerPoint, has died (www.washingtonpost.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/obituaries/2023/09/08/dennis-austin-software-developer-powerpoint-dies/</link>
            <guid>https://www.washingtonpost.com/obituaries/2023/09/08/dennis-austin-software-developer-powerpoint-dies/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 11:42:16 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Dennis Austin, Principal Software Developer of PowerPoint, Dies at 76']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dennis Austin, the principal software developer of PowerPoint, has passed away at the age of 76. Austin played a significant role in shaping how information is communicated in modern society through the development of PowerPoint. The software, which was released in 1987, revolutionized the creation of slides and became a ubiquitous tool in offices, classrooms, and government agencies. Despite its widespread use, PowerPoint has also faced criticism for its potential to create mind-numbing presentations filled with bullet points. Austin's contributions to the software were instrumental in its success.
            </p><p>
                140 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37444257">85 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public restrooms are hard to find in America (www.washingtonpost.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/09/08/public-restrooms-hard-find-comic/</link>
            <guid>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/09/08/public-restrooms-hard-find-comic/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 14:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['The Problem of Inaccessible Public Restrooms in America']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Public restrooms are hard to find in America, with only eight public toilets for every 100,000 people. This poses a problem for millions of Americans suffering from medical conditions, as well as unhoused individuals, older adults, and pregnant individuals. The lack of accessible public restrooms can lead to anxiety and avoidance of going out. This article highlights the importance of addressing this issue for the well-being of various populations.
            </p><p>
                64 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37446083">140 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morocco earthquake kills more than 1,000 (www.nbcnews.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/live-blog/morocco-earthquake-kills-600-devastates-historic-sites-live-updates-rcna104208</link>
            <guid>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/live-blog/morocco-earthquake-kills-600-devastates-historic-sites-live-updates-rcna104208</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:40:15 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Morocco Earthquake Claims Over 1,000 Lives and Devastates Historic Sites: Live Updates']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At least 1,037 people have been killed and over 1,200 injured in a 6.8-magnitude earthquake that struck Morocco. The epicenter was in the Moroccan High Atlas mountain range, southeast of Marrakech. Rescue efforts are underway, with the Moroccan army mobilizing search and rescue teams using helicopters and drones. The U.S. Embassy in Rabat has extended condolences and is not aware of any U.S. nationals affected.
            </p><p>
                136 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445284">86 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What happens when you shift a register by more than the register size? (devblogs.microsoft.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230904-00/?p=108704</link>
            <guid>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20230904-00/?p=108704</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 22:39:13 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Different Processor Architectures Behave Differently When Shifting Registers]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When shifting a register by more than its size, different processor architectures exhibit different behaviors. The table provided in the article shows the behavior of various processors, including the 8086, Alpha AXP, x86-64, MIPS, PowerPC, and more. The article also mentions that the C and C++ languages leave the behavior undefined when shifting by more than the bit width of the shifted type.
            </p><p>
                64 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37426598">40 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eio 1.0 – Effects-based IO for OCaml 5 (icfp23.sigplan.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://icfp23.sigplan.org/details/ocaml-2023-papers/5/Eio-1-0-Effects-based-IO-for-OCaml-5</link>
            <guid>https://icfp23.sigplan.org/details/ocaml-2023-papers/5/Eio-1-0-Effects-based-IO-for-OCaml-5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 08:44:07 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Eio 1.0 - Effects-based IO for OCaml 5' to be Presented at ICFP 2023]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This session at ICFP 2023 will discuss Eio 1.0, an effects-based IO stack for OCaml 5. The talk will cover its main features, including multi-core support, lock-free data structures, modular programming, interoperability with other concurrency libraries, and interactive monitoring support. The speakers will also share their experiences in porting existing applications to Eio.
            </p><p>
                7 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37443395">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Telescript Programming Language (en.wikipedia.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Telescript_(programming_language)</link>
            <guid>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Telescript_(programming_language)</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 04:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Telescript: An Agent-Oriented Programming Language for Uploading Programs to Servers']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Telescript is an agent-oriented programming language developed by General Magic as part of the Magic Cap system. It allowed end-user devices to upload programs to servers and take advantage of their capabilities. However, General Magic failed to find a niche in the market and Telescript services were eventually deprecated. The language was object-oriented and used a modified C-like syntax. It introduced the concepts of agents and places, which interacted with each other to perform tasks.
            </p><p>
                11 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37429362">1 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google's Statement on the UK Online Safety Bill (bills.parliament.uk)]]></title>
            <link>https://bills.parliament.uk/publications/46675/documents/1885</link>
            <guid>https://bills.parliament.uk/publications/46675/documents/1885</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:36:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Security Check on bills.parliament.uk]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The website bills.parliament.uk is checking the security of the user's connection before proceeding. It is using Cloudflare for performance and security. The Ray ID provided is 803f9d175da16464.
            </p><p>
                48 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37443634">27 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced NLP with SpaCy (course.spacy.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://course.spacy.io/en/</link>
            <guid>https://course.spacy.io/en/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 05:36:22 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Mastering Natural Language Processing with spaCy]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This course on spaCy, a Python library for Natural Language Processing, covers the basics of text processing, large-scale data analysis, processing pipelines, and training neural network models. It teaches you how to extract specific information from text, combine statistical and rule-based approaches, customize spaCy's models, and build advanced natural language understanding systems. The course is free and interactive, and is taught by Ines, one of the core developers of spaCy. She specializes in modern developer tools for AI, Machine Learning, and NLP.
            </p><p>
                87 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37442574">32 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Common Pitfalls in Database Performance Testing (2018) [pdf] (news.ycombinator.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37413926</link>
            <guid>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37413926</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 02:16:49 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No summary available
            </p><p>
                30 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37413926">8 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart people first in line for Covid-19 vaccines, study suggests (www.cidrap.umn.edu)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/smart-people-first-line-covid-19-vaccines-study-suggests</link>
            <guid>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/smart-people-first-line-covid-19-vaccines-study-suggests</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 17:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Study Suggests Intelligent People Get COVID-19 Vaccines Faster']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Intelligent people are getting COVID-19 vaccines faster than those with lower cognitive abilities, according to a study in Sweden. The study found that 80% of the most intelligent people were vaccinated within 40 days of vaccine availability, while it took 180 days for those with the lowest cognitive ability to reach that level. The researchers suggest that the complexity of the vaccination decision may make it difficult for people with lower cognitive abilities to understand the benefits of vaccination. The findings highlight the need for better-designed vaccination campaigns to address disparities in vaccination behavior.
            </p><p>
                6 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37447833">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning Zig (www.openmymind.net)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.openmymind.net/learning_zig/</link>
            <guid>https://www.openmymind.net/learning_zig/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 15:28:44 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA['Learning Zig: An Introduction to the Zig Programming Language']]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This guide provides an introduction to the Zig programming language, assuming prior programming experience. It covers topics such as installing Zig, language overview, style guide, memory management, generics, and coding in Zig. The guide emphasizes that Zig is under heavy development and may have code discrepancies. It also provides instructions for installing Zig and testing the setup.
            </p><p>
                64 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37446502">12 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Show HN: It's Like HN, but for Science (synthical.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://synthical.com/feed/simple</link>
            <guid>https://synthical.com/feed/simple</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 14:33:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Studies on Marine Metabolome, Catalysts, and Materials Engineering Published by Researchers]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researchers at various universities have published studies on a range of topics including the deep metabolome of marine dissolved organic matter, CO2-assisted propane ODH over catalysts, synthesis of N-acyl carbazoles, and the use of artificial peroxidase based on biotin-streptavidin technology. Other studies cover topics such as microcapsules with amphiphilic polymer conetwork shells, collision-induced unfolding of mitochondrial tRNAs, and the use of Rare Earth Elements on high-tech materials engineering. These studies contribute to the fields of analytical chemistry, organic chemistry, catalysis, and more.
            </p><p>
                9 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37445905">4 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Food for People with Dementia (www.newyorker.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/personal-history/the-power-of-food-for-people-with-dementia</link>
            <guid>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/personal-history/the-power-of-food-for-people-with-dementia</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 01:15:10 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Transformative Role of Food for Individuals with Dementia]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Power of Food in Triggering Memories and Enhancing Quality of Life for People with Dementia
            </p><p>
                103 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37413566">28 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-time Trumpet Simulation C++/Vulkan [video] (www.youtube.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rGNUHigqUBM</link>
            <guid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rGNUHigqUBM</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 13:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[N/A]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>N/A
            </p><p>
                22 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37418278">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>