<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
        <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        <description>HN posts' summary</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 02:37:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Feed for Node.js</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <image>
            <title>Hacker News Summary</title>
            <url>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/b2/Y_Combinator_logo.svg/500px-Y_Combinator_logo.svg.png</url>
            <link>https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary</link>
        </image>
        <category>Frontpage</category>
        <atom:link href="https://ruanyf.github.io/hnsummary/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoded: GNU Coreutils (2018) (maizure.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://maizure.org/projects/decoded-gnu-coreutils/</link>
            <guid>https://maizure.org/projects/decoded-gnu-coreutils/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:15:52 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Decoding the GNU coreutils: Exploring the Design of Command-Line Utilities]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decoding the GNU coreutils version 8.3 is a long-term project aimed at providing useful background for novice programmers exploring the design of command-line utilities. The project is divided into phases, with Phase 1 and Phase 2 already complete. Phase 1 focused on discussing the namespace and execution overview of each utility, while Phase 2 expanded on important design decisions and algorithms. The project also aims to provide a line-by-line code walkthrough for each utility in the future. The GNU coreutils, which are small, single-source file programs, have their own unique design patterns and often rely on the Getopt toolset for parsing command line options. The utilities also make use of the fts library for traversing the file system and include syscall wrappers and helpers from the Gnulib project. Overall, the project provides helpful insights into the design and implementation of the GNU coreutils.
            </p><p>
                147 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37439535">36 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Snoop unto them as they snoop unto you (blog.dataparty.xyz)]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/snoop-unto-them/</link>
            <guid>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/snoop-unto-them/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 22:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[DEFCON 31 Releases Official Videos and Offers Support Options]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DEFCON 31 has released official videos of their talks, including 'Snoop unto them as they snoop unto you'. The talk, slides, files, and code are available for download. The blog post also provides links to support the speakers through buying them a coffee, getting their product rfparty, and following them on various social media platforms. The post ends with an invitation to join their Discord server and sign up for their mailing list.
            </p><p>
                75 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37440104">35 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Most bees live underground. X-ray images reveal how they build their nests (www.science.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.science.org/content/article/most-bees-live-underground-x-ray-images-reveal-how-they-build-their-nests</link>
            <guid>https://www.science.org/content/article/most-bees-live-underground-x-ray-images-reveal-how-they-build-their-nests</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:17:21 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Security Check Required for Access to www.science.org]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The website www.science.org is checking the security of your connection before allowing access. This is likely due to the use of Cloudflare for performance and security. The Ray ID provided is 803b4673adb9ce94. It is important for websites to ensure secure connections to protect user data. The review process is necessary to prevent unauthorized access or data breaches. Once the security check is completed, users will be able to proceed to the website.
            </p><p>
                4 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37440482">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The rxv64 Operating System: MIT's xv6, in Rust, for SMP x86_64 machines (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/dancrossnyc/rxv64</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/dancrossnyc/rxv64</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:03:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[rxv64: A Pedagogical Operating System Reimplementation of xv6 in Rust]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>rxv64 is a pedagogical operating system written in Rust that targets multiprocessor x86_64 machines. It is a reimplementation of the xv6 operating system from MIT. The system supports limited hardware including the text-mode CGA device, serial port, PS/2 keyboard controller, and PCIe AHCI SATA storage devices. The xv6 README provides more information on its origin and intended use.
            </p><p>
                4 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37439391">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LogoScale – A method for vectorizing small, crappy logos (msprout.notion.site)]]></title>
            <link>https://msprout.notion.site/LogoScale-A-Method-for-Vectorizing-Small-Crappy-Logos-dc0035b7473c44f8b94ffc4026d286c0</link>
            <guid>https://msprout.notion.site/LogoScale-A-Method-for-Vectorizing-Small-Crappy-Logos-dc0035b7473c44f8b94ffc4026d286c0</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:38:39 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[N/A]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>N/A
            </p><p>
                5 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37440631">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scammers can exploit email forwarding flaws to impersonate high-profile domains (today.ucsd.edu)]]></title>
            <link>https://today.ucsd.edu/story/forwarding_based_spoofing</link>
            <guid>https://today.ucsd.edu/story/forwarding_based_spoofing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 19:45:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Security Flaws in Email Forwarding Allow Scammers to Impersonate High-profile Domains]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researchers at the University of California San Diego have discovered security flaws in the email forwarding process that allow scammers to impersonate high-profile domains. This vulnerability affects tens of thousands of domains, including government organizations, financial service companies, and major news organizations. The researchers found that scammers can send spoofed emails that bypass the safeguards of email providers like Gmail and Outlook, increasing the likelihood of recipients opening malicious attachments or clicking on harmful links. The vulnerabilities arise from the delegation of email infrastructure to third-party providers and the assumption that each organization operates its own mailing infrastructure. While some providers have patched the issues, the researchers recommend disabling open forwarding and implementing stricter validation policies to address the root problem.
            </p><p>
                87 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438478">31 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using LD_PRELOAD to cheat, inject features and investigate programs (rafalcieslak.wordpress.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://rafalcieslak.wordpress.com/2013/04/02/dynamic-linker-tricks-using-ld_preload-to-cheat-inject-features-and-investigate-programs/</link>
            <guid>https://rafalcieslak.wordpress.com/2013/04/02/dynamic-linker-tricks-using-ld_preload-to-cheat-inject-features-and-investigate-programs/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:41:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manipulating Application Behavior with LD_PRELOAD]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Using LD_PRELOAD to manipulate the behavior of applications
            </p><p>
                80 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37439125">50 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generally Intelligent (YC S17) Is Hiring Technical Interviewers (news.ycombinator.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37441168</link>
            <guid>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37441168</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 01:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No summary available
            </p><p>
                1 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37441168">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Show HN: Conway's Game of Life in TypeScript's type system (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/RuyiLi/cursed-typescript/blob/master/random/game-of-life.ts</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/RuyiLi/cursed-typescript/blob/master/random/game-of-life.ts</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 19:11:47 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Code File for TypeScript Implementation of Game of Life]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a code file for a TypeScript implementation of the Game of Life. The code consists of 203 lines and is approximately 7.24 KB in size. It appears to be a random file within a larger project called 'cursed-typescript'.
            </p><p>
                113 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438028">31 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aardvark'd: The Fog Creek documentary, 18 years later (mtlynch.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://mtlynch.io/aardvarkd/</link>
            <guid>https://mtlynch.io/aardvarkd/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 13:26:45 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Aardvark'd: The Fog Creek Documentary, 18 Years Later - A Look into the Early Days of Tech Startup Founders]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aardvark'd: The Fog Creek Documentary, 18 Years Later is a documentary film about Fog Creek's summer internship program in 2005. The film captures interviews with individuals who would go on to achieve fame and success in the tech industry. It explores the indie software scene of 2005, featuring Fog Creek Software, Y Combinator, and the launch of reddit. The documentary showcases the vulnerability and uncertainty experienced by tech startup founders during their early days. Despite its flaws, Aardvark'd provides a relatable and engaging look into the challenges of launching a software product. The film ends without a clear resolution, leaving viewers wondering about the outcome of the interns' project. The documentary includes insightful quotes from Paul Graham and Aaron Swartz. Surprisingly, Fog Creek did not finance the film, and the filmmaker recently uploaded it for free on YouTube.
            </p><p>
                370 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37433186">128 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Just how constexpr is C++20’s std:string? (quuxplusone.github.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://quuxplusone.github.io/blog/2023/09/08/constexpr-string-firewall/</link>
            <guid>https://quuxplusone.github.io/blog/2023/09/08/constexpr-string-firewall/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:23:27 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the constexprness of C++20's std::string]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>C++20's std::string and std::vector can be marked as constexpr, allowing them to be used in compile-time programming. However, there are two constraints on constexprness: the value cannot depend on runtime input, and certain data cannot flow from compile-time into runtime. The article explains these constraints using examples of stack variables and memory addresses. It also discusses the limitations of constexpr string and vector, such as the inability to escape pointers to their data and the impact of small string optimization (SSO). The intended use of constexpr string and vector is as local variables or return types of constexpr or consteval functions, rather than as constexpr or constinit variables.
            </p><p>
                81 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37431425">59 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bun v1.0.0 (github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://github.com/oven-sh/bun/releases/tag/bun-v1.0.0</link>
            <guid>https://github.com/oven-sh/bun/releases/tag/bun-v1.0.0</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 14:41:03 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bun v1.0 Release: Bug Fixes, Improvements, and New Features]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bun v1.0 is now available for installation and upgrade. The release notes highlight various bug fixes and improvements, including fixes for sourcemaps, hot reloading, module imports, debugger support, and more. The release also brings in uSockets and uWebSockets forks into Bun's repository. The changelog lists all the changes made from version 0.8.1 to 1.0.0. The release has seen contributions from new contributors as well. Overall, Bun v1.0 offers several enhancements and bug fixes for a better development experience.
            </p><p>
                730 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37434117">245 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Losing Out in Critical Technologies: Cisco Systems and Financialization (www.ineteconomics.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.ineteconomics.org/perspectives/blog/losing-out-in-critical-technologies-cisco-systems-and-financialization</link>
            <guid>https://www.ineteconomics.org/perspectives/blog/losing-out-in-critical-technologies-cisco-systems-and-financialization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 06:34:22 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cisco Systems' Financialization and its Impact on US Technology Competitiveness]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cisco Systems, once a global leader in telecommunication systems and the Internet, has fallen behind global competitors in critical technologies such as 5G and IoT. This is due to the company's shift from innovation to financialization, prioritizing stock buybacks over investments in cutting-edge communication-infrastructure products. Since 2001, Cisco has spent $152.3 billion on stock buybacks, wasting funds that could have been used for technological advancements. The company's focus on maximizing shareholder value has hindered its competitive position in the US information-and-communication-technology industry. This article explores Cisco's transformation from an innovative enterprise to a financialized one and discusses the implications for the industry's global competitiveness.
            </p><p>
                3 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37415456">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maybe Rust isn’t a good tool for massively concurrent, userspace software (bitbashing.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://bitbashing.io/async-rust.html</link>
            <guid>https://bitbashing.io/async-rust.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 16:10:55 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Challenges and Limitations of Async Rust for Concurrency]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The article discusses the challenges and limitations of using async Rust for concurrency. It explains the difference between parallelism and concurrency and how breaking a problem into separate, independent parts can improve performance. The author explores the use of threads and mutex-based concurrency, highlighting the drawbacks and complexities involved. They then introduce the concept of channels as a synchronization mechanism and discuss how many modern languages, including Rust, provide channels in their standard libraries. The article also delves into the unique challenges of async Rust, such as the need to assure the compiler of data safety and the limitations of using Arc for dynamic lifetimes. Overall, the author suggests that while Rust may not be the best tool for massively concurrent, userspace software, it can still be valuable for other projects.
            </p><p>
                500 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37435515">418 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexport is rescinding a bunch of signed offer letters (twitter.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://twitter.com/typesfast/status/1700092765798048093</link>
            <guid>https://twitter.com/typesfast/status/1700092765798048093</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 14:07:55 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Twitter Requires Switch to Supported Browser]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twitter no longer supports this browser and users are advised to switch to a supported browser in order to continue using the platform. The Help Center provides a list of supported browsers for reference. The message also includes links to the Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, Cookie Policy, and Imprint. The copyright information indicates that it is © 2023 X Corp.
            </p><p>
                220 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37433681">253 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delivery of gene therapy through CSF conduit to rescue hearing in adult mice (www.science.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/scitranslmed.abq3916</link>
            <guid>https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/scitranslmed.abq3916</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 23:21:52 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Security Review Requested for www.science.org]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The website www.science.org is requesting to review the security of the user's connection before proceeding. This is likely due to concerns about potential security risks or vulnerabilities. The website is utilizing Cloudflare for performance and security purposes. The specific Ray ID provided is 803b0eb75fbdcf4d, which may be used for tracking or troubleshooting purposes. It is important for users to ensure the security of their connection before accessing the website.
            </p><p>
                3 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37412738">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uber CEO’s time moonlighting as a driver sparked all-hands called 'Why we suck.' (www.businessinsider.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/uber-ceo-dara-khosrowshahi-company-should-have-paid-attention-drivers-2023-9</link>
            <guid>https://www.businessinsider.com/uber-ceo-dara-khosrowshahi-company-should-have-paid-attention-drivers-2023-9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:55:01 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Uber CEO's Time as a Driver Reveals Lack of Quality in Driver Product]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uber CEO Dara Khosrowshahi reveals that his time as a driver for the company showed him a lack of quality in the driver product. He made an all-hands presentation titled 'Why we suck' based on his experiences. Khosrowshahi realized that the company was too focused on the rider and eater product and didn't pay enough attention to the driver product. He later shared what he learned with the company and set a new expectation. Despite his experiences, Khosrowshahi underestimated the cost of an Uber ride in New York City. 
            </p><p>
                21 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37441125">20 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA['How Do You Know When Your Art Is Good?' (www.ask-polly.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.ask-polly.com/p/how-do-you-know-when-your-art-is</link>
            <guid>https://www.ask-polly.com/p/how-do-you-know-when-your-art-is</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 23:39:18 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Embracing Uncertainty and Enduring Pain: The Journey of an Artist]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the uncertainty of artistic success and the fear of judgment is a natural part of the creative process. The author shares their own experiences of self-doubt and the importance of tolerating discomfort in order to grow as an artist. They emphasize that feeling negative and upset about one's art is a sign of caring deeply about it, and that enduring the pain of creating art can ultimately make one stronger. The article concludes by highlighting the universal fear of being unloved and the transformative power of facing that fear through art.
            </p><p>
                4 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37412887">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artic Code Vault (archiveprogram.github.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://archiveprogram.github.com/arctic-vault/</link>
            <guid>https://archiveprogram.github.com/arctic-vault/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:16:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[GitHub Creates Arctic Code Vault to Preserve Open Source Software]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>GitHub has created the Arctic Code Vault, a data repository stored in the Arctic World Archive (AWA) to preserve a snapshot of every active public repository as of 02/02/2020. The AWA is a long-term archival facility located in a decommissioned coal mine in the Svalbard archipelago. The archive is designed to last 1,000 years and is considered a stable site for preserving humanity's collective knowledge. The 02/02/2020 snapshot, consisting of 21TB of data, was stored on 186 reels of film and transported to the Arctic Code Vault. To recognize contributions, GitHub created the Arctic Code Vault Badge displayed on developers' profiles. The vault contains open source software from millions of developers worldwide.
            </p><p>
                14 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37429645">10 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerabyte: ceramic storage poised to usher in 'yottabyte era' (www.tomshardware.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/cerabyte-ceramic-storage-poised-to-usher-in-yottabyte-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.tomshardware.com/news/cerabyte-ceramic-storage-poised-to-usher-in-yottabyte-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 16:49:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cerabyte's Ceramic Storage Technology Aims to Revolutionize the Market]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cerabyte, a German storage startup, claims that its ceramic nanolayer-based storage technology will disrupt the storage market by reducing data center storage TCO by 75%. The company plans to introduce CeraMemory cartridges (2025-30) with storage capacities between 10 PB and 100 PB, and CeraTape (2030-35) with up to 1 EB capacity per tape. Cerabyte's technology uses inorganic nanolayers to store information and can read and write data at GB/s class speeds. The company also highlights the durability and longevity of its ceramic storage, claiming that it can last over 5,000 years and withstand extreme temperatures and environments. Cerabyte's presentation at the 2023 Storage Developer Conference is highly anticipated.
            </p><p>
                85 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37436092">31 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards a new SymPy (oscarbenjamin.github.io)]]></title>
            <link>https://oscarbenjamin.github.io/blog/czi/post1.html</link>
            <guid>https://oscarbenjamin.github.io/blog/czi/post1.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:50:49 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Foundations of a Computer Algebra System: Towards a Faster SymPy]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Towards a Faster SymPy: Part 1 - Outlining the Foundations of a Computer Algebra System
            </p><p>
                100 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37430759">45 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GitHubGuessr (github-guessr.vercel.app)]]></title>
            <link>https://github-guessr.vercel.app/</link>
            <guid>https://github-guessr.vercel.app/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:09:44 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[N/A]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>N/A
            </p><p>
                58 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37432067">27 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Touch Pianist (touchpianist.com)]]></title>
            <link>http://touchpianist.com/</link>
            <guid>http://touchpianist.com/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:56:08 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Menu of Pieces on a Mobile App]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a brief summary of a menu or selection of pieces available on a mobile app. The menu offers the option to choose a different piece and provides information about the app and its creator. It mentions that the app is available for free on Android and iOS platforms. The content seems to be truncated, so it is difficult to provide a more detailed summary.
            </p><p>
                584 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37431644">186 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Learn Emacs (2012) (david.rothlis.net)]]></title>
            <link>https://david.rothlis.net/emacs/howtolearn.html</link>
            <guid>https://david.rothlis.net/emacs/howtolearn.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 20:16:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Mastering Emacs: A Guide for Programmers]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This guide to Emacs is aimed at computer programmers who want to master the text editor. It acknowledges that the learning curve for Emacs is steep but promises to help users reach the next level of programming in months rather than years. The guide emphasizes self-driven discovery using Emacs' built-in help, debugging facilities, and source code. The author asks for commitment and patience from readers, urging them to give up their favorite IDE's features for at least a month or two. The next section explores why Emacs is worth the effort.
            </p><p>
                52 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37438842">21 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Debugging Catastrophic Backtracking for Regular Expressions in Python (krishnanchandra.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://krishnanchandra.com/posts/regex-catastrophic-backtracking/</link>
            <guid>https://krishnanchandra.com/posts/regex-catastrophic-backtracking/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 17:22:12 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Fixing Catastrophic Backtracking in Regular Expressions in Python]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fixing catastrophic backtracking in regular expressions in Python by using a non-greedy pattern. The article discusses how a regex pattern with a greedy subpattern can lead to exponential runtime on strings with many newlines, causing the application to become stuck. By making the repeating subpattern non-greedy and adding the re.DOTALL flag to match newlines, the runtime becomes linear instead of exponential. The article provides a comparison of the performance between the problematic regex and the fixed regex using a test script. The results show that the problematic regex performs poorly on long input sequences, while the fixed regex scales much better. The article concludes with a log-log plot illustrating the exponential relationship between input size and execution time for the problematic regex.
            </p><p>
                3 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37422355">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASMesh: Anonymous, Secure Messaging in Mesh Networks (eprint.iacr.org)]]></title>
            <link>https://eprint.iacr.org/2023/1053</link>
            <guid>https://eprint.iacr.org/2023/1053</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:24:25 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ASMesh: Anonymous and Secure Messaging in Mesh Networks Using Stronger, Anonymous Double Ratchet]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ASMesh is a new protocol that provides anonymous and secure messaging in mesh networks. It addresses the limitations of centralized service providers in scenarios like mass protests in censored networks. The protocol is designed to achieve forward and post-compromise security, as well as forward and post-compromise anonymity. It builds on Signal's Double Ratchet protocol and introduces enhancements to ensure strong confidentiality and anonymity under user corruptions. The protocol's security is proven and its performance is evaluated in simulated mesh networks. The paper also includes a proof of concept implementation.
            </p><p>
                5 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37431433">0 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Critical ignoring as a core competence for digital citizens (2022) (journals.sagepub.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/epub/10.1177/09637214221121570</link>
            <guid>https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/epub/10.1177/09637214221121570</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 03:36:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Website Security Check: journals.sagepub.com]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The website journals.sagepub.com is requesting to review the security of the user's connection before proceeding. This is likely due to concerns about potential security risks or vulnerabilities. The website is utilizing Cloudflare for performance and security purposes. The specific Ray ID provided is a unique identifier for the user's connection. It is important for users to ensure that their connection is secure before proceeding with any sensitive activities on the website.
            </p><p>
                145 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37428937">102 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atari pulls nostalgia power move and buys homebrew community forum (www.theregister.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.theregister.com/2023/09/08/atari_snaps_up_atariage/</link>
            <guid>https://www.theregister.com/2023/09/08/atari_snaps_up_atariage/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 00:20:36 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Atari Acquires Retro Gaming Forum AtariAge to Enhance IP and Games]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Atari acquires retro gaming forum AtariAge to enhance its IP and games available for its hardware. The founder of AtariAge will become Atari's internal historian, and Atari has promised not to censor speech on the forums. The acquisition has been mostly met with approval by the community, as enthusiasm for an obsolete platform alone is not sustainable. However, some users have expressed concerns about monetization and Atari's reputation. The acquisition aligns with Atari's plans to revive the 2600 console and support vintage cartridges.
            </p><p>
                15 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37440943">3 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The thinking path (www.robinsloan.com)]]></title>
            <link>https://www.robinsloan.com/newsletters/what-would-a-wizard-read/#walking</link>
            <guid>https://www.robinsloan.com/newsletters/what-would-a-wizard-read/#walking</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 21:52:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Robin Sloan's Excitement for His New Novel and Reflections on Creativity and Goodness]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robin Sloan announces the upcoming publication of his new novel in June 2024 and shares his excitement. He discusses the influence of fantasy sagas on his previous novels and explores the idea of going beyond homage to actively participate in the genre. Sloan plans to create a rich introduction and companion for his new novel, incorporating various influences and media. He also reviews a novel by Michiko Aoyama and reflects on the need for creative investigations of decency and goodness. Sloan asks for nominations of great author websites and discusses the problem-solving power of walking. He concludes by highlighting the quality of science journalism and sharing an interesting logo treatment for Mattel Electronics.
            </p><p>
                132 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37426107">30 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digging through the New York Times morgue (buttondown.email)]]></title>
            <link>https://buttondown.email/linotypebook/archive/lbp-issue-no-5-digging-through-a-morgue/</link>
            <guid>https://buttondown.email/linotypebook/archive/lbp-issue-no-5-digging-through-a-morgue/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 21:53:14 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Uncovering Treasures: Exploring the Transition to Computer Phototypesetting at The New York Times]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researcher uncovers treasures from the transition to computer phototypesetting in the 1970s while digging through the New York Times morgue. The morgue contains millions of newspaper clippings, photographs, and other materials organized by subject matter. The researcher explores the transition from hot metal composition to computer phototypesetting at The Times in the 1970s, delving into the reasons behind the newspaper's delayed adoption of the technology. The visit to the morgue reveals internal publications documenting the transition and photos of the typesetting room. The researcher shares their process of organizing and analyzing the materials for their book on the topic.
            </p><p>
                25 Points |  <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=37426116">7 comments</a>
            </p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>